美国家庭影院 出品
联合制作: 梦工厂 与 PLAYTON公司
领衔主演:迈克尔・库德利兹 里克・格梅兹 斯科特・格里米斯
弗兰克・约翰・休伊斯 达米安・路易斯 朗・利文斯通
詹姆斯・马迪欧 尼尔・麦克唐纳 雷内・L・莫雷诺
马泰・塞特尔 道格拉斯・斯佩恩 理察・斯贝特
唐尼・沃尔伯格 里克・沃登 马可・沃伦
角色的分派: 利伯曼/巴顿
视觉效果总监:安格斯・ 比克尔顿
特殊效果监督员: 乔斯・威廉姆斯
服装设计师: 安娜・谢帕德
编辑:诺里・奥蒂
音乐:迈克尔・凯曼
制作设计 : 安东尼・布拉特
摄影指导:乔尔・ J・ 兰塞姆
监督指导: 艾力克・简得森
制作人: 玛丽・理查兹
监督制片人: 埃里克・ 柏克
联合执行制片人: 史蒂芬・安布洛斯 加里・高依兹曼 托尼・ 托
执行制片人:汤姆・汉克斯 斯蒂文・斯皮尔伯格
兄弟连作者: 史蒂芬・安布洛斯
写作:E・马克斯・弗赖伊
导演:米卡埃尔・所罗门
兄 弟 连
I never thought I'd get through D-day.
我从没想过能活过D日
Let alone the next phase or the next phase.
更不用说接下来的阶段
I thought I was going to get killed instantly.
我以为我马上就会阵亡
I thought one of two things:
我想只有两种下场
A quick death or...
要不是很快就阵亡
...I'd come through probably without a scratch.
不然就可能是毫发无伤
I think everybody had fear.
我想每个人都有恐惧
I think there's people that can handle fear.
有人也知道如何面对恐怖
I think...
我想
I think I was probably one of them.
我就是这样的人
I think I was just as...
尽管我和其他人
...scared as anybody else except I could think.
一样害怕 只是我还能够思考
It's a feeling you would not let yourself down...
这是一种不能让自己丢脸的感觉
...and you would not let your comrades or your unit down.
更不能让弟兄和连队丢脸
We all had fear.
我们心里都有着恐惧
But we all had training to know that...
但是我们都受过训练去了解
...you try to handle your fear...
你要试着去战胜恐惧
...and work to accomplish what you're supposed to be doing.
努力完成你该做的事
第三集
卡 灵 顿
( 1944年6月8日 )
( 法国 诺曼底 )
Hey, it looks like what's-his-name.
那家伙叫什么名字来着?
You know, from 1st Platoon?
就是第一排的那家伙
Our 1st platoon?
我们连的第一排?
It sure does.
废话
Blithe.
布洛依
Hey, Blithe.
嘿 布洛依
Blithe!
布洛依!
Thought that was you.
我就知道是你
You alone?
就你一个人?
You're the first familiar faces I've seen.
你是我遇到的第一个熟人
I ain't surprised.
没什么好奇怪
They dropped us all over the peninsula.
他们把我们在柯胜丁半岛丢得到处都是
We've been fighting with the 502nd since we hit the ground.
我们降落之后 一直跟着502团作战
You?
你呢?
Oh, I've been...
我一直...
...trying to find Easy.
在找Ｅ连的人
Join the club.
跟我们一起走吧
Hey, fellows.
伙计们
Well, look who decided to show up, Floyd.
看看是谁终于露脸了 佛洛依德
Hi there, Luz.
鲁兹 你还好吗?
We thought we'd never find you guys.
我们还以为再也找不到你们了
Hey, Tab, get a load of this.
泰仔! 看看这个 挺不错的!
You like that?
喜不喜欢?
It's the real stuff.
喜欢 这可是真材实料呢
Yeah, of course.
当然了
You like this?
你喜欢吗?
Oh, nice.
不错
That's a beauty, Sarge.
- 这真是好东西 中士 - 迷彩真好看 泰柏特
My Luger's gonna put you all to shame when I get it.
等我拿到我的鲁格枪 你们通通都会羞愧至死
How was your jump?
你们跳得如何?
Missed the DZ.
错过了降落地点
Yeah, that goes without saying.
那还用得着说吗?
I guess so.
我想也是
Got any souvenirs to trade?
有什么纪念品要交换吗?
What?
什么?
They're all ticking.
它们都还能走
Unlike their previous owners.
不象它们的前主人
Got anything good?
有什么好东西吗?
Not yet.
还没有
Hey.
好吧
So, have we lost anybody?
我们有损失弟兄吗?
Tommy Burgess took one in the face.
汤米伯基斯脸部挂彩
Popeye Wynn got pinked in the behind.
"普派"怀恩屁股开花
But they're gonna be okay.
不过他们都会没事的
That's good.
那就好
You run into Lt. Meehan on your travels?
你一路上有遇到米汉中尉吗?
No, why?
没有 为什么这么问?
Company HQ's still missing.
还联系不上连指挥所
They think the plane crashed.
有人认为飞机被击落了
They say he's gonna turn up.
有人认为他会出现的
Yeah, I ain't holding my breath.
我可不那么想
Who's in command, then?
那现在谁是指挥官?
Winters for now.
现在是由温特斯指挥
Lieutenant Welsh is 1st Platoon.
威尔旭中尉负责第一排
Let's go, 1st Platoon!
第一排出发!
Easy's moving out!
Ｅ连出发了!
On your feet.
第一排起立
Stand up, lift up. Let's go.
起立 我们出发了
Listen up!
注意!
It'll be dark soon.
天快黑了
I want light and noise discipline from here on.
从现在开始 我要实施噪音及灯火管制
No talking, no smoking.
不准说话 不准抽烟
No playing grab-fanny with the man in front of you, Luz.
也不准抓前面人的屁股 鲁兹
So, where we headed to, Lieutenant?
我们要去哪里 中尉?
We're taking Carentan.
去攻占卡灵顿
That sounds like fun.
听起来很好玩
It's the only place where armor from Omaha and Utah Beach...
那是奥马哈和犹他滩头的装甲部队
...can link up and head inland.
唯一可以集结向内陆挺进的地点
Until we take it, they're stuck on the sand.
在我们拿下卡灵顿前 他们将困在沙滩上
General Taylor's sending the whole division.
泰勒将军已经派了整个师
Remember, boys...
各位弟兄记住
...give me three days and three nights of hard fighting...
你们好好奋战三天三夜
...and you will be relieved.
我就让你们休假
Lieutenant.
中尉
Lieutenant, I'll take point.
我来担任尖兵
Corporal Hoobler will be lead scout.
胡伯勒下士带领搜索组
Blithe, glad you could join us.
布洛依! 很高兴你能加入我们
Thank you, sir.
谢谢你 长官
1st Platoon, fall in behind Fox Company.
第一排 在Ｆ连后面集合
You people from 2nd and 3rd Platoon, follow us.
第二及第三排跟着我们
Let's shake a leg.
我们出发了
Another thing to remember, boys...
再提醒你们一件事 弟兄们
...flies spread disease.
"苍蝇"会传染疾病
So, keep yours closed.
所以把你的给关好了
Don't wake Jerry.
别把德军吵醒了
- Damn! - What?
- 该死! - 怎么了?
We lost F Company, sir.
我们跟丢了Ｆ连 长官
Again?
又跟丢了?
We lost F Company.
我们跟丢了Ｆ连
Again?
又跟丢了?
Hey, Blithe, Skinny, guess what?
布洛依 史基尼 你猜怎么着?
- Perconte, go tell them to hold up. - Yes, sir.
- 派康提 去叫部队停止前进 - 是 长官!
- Hoobler, take Blithe, go find F Company. - Yes, sir.
- 胡伯勒 带布洛依去找Ｆ连 - 是 长官!
Come on, Blithe.
走吧 布洛依
Shit.
该死
Did you send somebody?
你有没有叫人去?
Hoobler and Blithe are there now.
有 胡伯勒和布洛依去找了
Why are we stopped?
我们为什么停下来?
This is about officers crapping out on their training, Nix.
尼克 都因为军官在训练的时侯开小差了
Come on, let's get this show on the road.
我们开始找吧
Dang mosquitoes.
可恶的蚊子
What is it?
怎么了?
Shh
嘘...
Flash.
电闪!
Thunder.
雷鸣!
I can hear y'll all the way across the field.
我大老远就听见你们的声音
You F Company?
你们是Ｆ连的吗?
That's right.
没错
Where you all been?
你们跑去哪里了?
Blithe, go back to the Lieutenant.
布洛依! 回去找中尉
Tell him we've found F Company.
就说我们找到Ｆ连了
I'll figure out where these yokels are.
我会标出这群乡巴佬的位置
Hey, who you all calling a yokel?
你说谁是乡巴佬?
He's dead, Private.
他已经死了 二等兵
Did you find Fox Company?
你们找到Ｆ连了吗?
Yes, sir.
是的 长官
I thought he...
我还以为他...
I thought he had me.
我还以为他逮到我了
Fallschirmjager.
德军空降兵部队
Paratrooper?
伞兵?
We think there's a regiment of them holding Carentan.
师部认为他们有一个团驻守在卡灵顿
Well, there's one less to worry about.
敌人又少了一个
Yeah.
对
That's edelweiss.
该死 这是雪绒花
That only grows in the Alps above the tree line...
它只生长在阿尔卑斯山脉雪线之上
...which means he climbed up there to get it.
这表示他真的爬到那么高的地方去摘它
It's supposed to be the mark of a true soldier.
这是真正军人的象征
( D日后第6天 )
( 法国 卡灵顿 )
Take the 1st straight up the middle...
我要你率领第一排直攻中路
...hard and fast.
要又快又狠
We must move quickly.
我们的行动必须迅速
I'll be right behind you with 2nd and 3rd.
我带第二 三排跟在你后面
Go!
上!
Let's go, 1st, let's go.
第一排上
Go, go, go!
上!
In the ditch!
躲进壕沟里!趴下!
Incoming!
敌人攻击!
God damn it!
可恶!
Where the fuck is everybody?
大伙都跑去哪里了?!
Where did everybody go?
大家都死到哪儿去了?!
I have no idea!
我不知道!
Let's go, Easy!
Ｅ连 我们上!
Get those MGs moving, will you?
逼德军机枪转移阵地!
Let's get them out of there.
让我们救出他们
They're in the open, for Pete's sake!
老天 他们暴露在空旷地!
Go, go!
上!
Get going, Buck.
叫大家快走 巴克
Follow me, Easy!
Ｅ连的跟着我!
Move out!
快点!
Move out, men!
快走!
Go!
向前进!
Move out, move out!
前进!
Get yourselves out of that ditch!
赶快从壕沟里出来!
We have men getting killed out there, Blithe!
外面有弟兄受到敌人攻击 布洛依!
Move!
快走!
Upstairs window, left.
压制火力 楼上左边窗户
Get yourselves out of those trenches!
快点离开壕沟!
Incoming!
遭到攻击!
That's an MG-42.
那是挺MG42机枪
There's one in the right upper...
右上方有一个...
Medic!
医护兵!
Upper flank!
上方!
Oh, shit!
可恶!
Snipers, that way...
狙击手
...take his lower left.
打他的左下
Ah, shit!
可恶
We need some covering fire. Ready, Luz?
我们需要掩护射击 准备好了吗 鲁兹?
Okay, I'm out.
好了! 我要出去了
Shit!
可恶!
Guarnere, clear that sector on the right!
葛奈瑞! 清除右方那个区域!
Hit them with me!
跟我一起!
You okay, Shifty?
你还好吗 西福弟?
We gotta take that warehouse!
我们得拿下那仓库!
Shifty!
西福弟!
Hammer those windows.
射击那些窗子
Tipper, take Liebgott, start clearing these buildings.
提波 带着李高特开始检查这些建筑
Right. Let's go!
好的 走
Second two, go, go!
二排二班! 上!
Houses on the right!
注意右边的房子!
Smash.
打破窗子
Grenade.
然后扔手榴弹进去
Luz, come on, Luz.
鲁兹 快点
Come on.
快点
Close behind.
就在你后面
Shit!
可恶!
They got us zeroed!
他们瞄准我们了!
Spread it out, spread it out!
快散开!
Go!
快点!
Get the hell out of there!
赶快离开那里!
They got us zeroed!
他们瞄准我们了!
Get out of there!
快离开那里!
Go, go!
快点!
Get the hell out of the street!
快离开那条街!
Move, now.
我们快走
Go, go, go!
走 走!
Come on, let's get you out of here.
我们带你离开这里
Come on, boy.
来吧
Move, move, move!
快走!
Get off the street!
快离开这条街!
Go, go!
快点!
Move it, now!
快点走!
Hey, buddy.
撑着点 兄弟
You're okay, Lip.
你没事 李普
Everything's right where it should be.
所有东西都在
Come on, upsy-daisy.
来! 我扶你起来
Get Tipper up here with the bazooka.
让提波带着火箭筒到这来
Hello?
有人吗?
Anybody there?
里面有人吗?
Tipper!
提波!
Tip!
Tipper!
提波!
Answer me, Tip!
回答我 提波!
Joe?
乔 是你吗?
Looking good, Tip.
看起来不错 提波
Is that you?
是你吗?
Looking real good.
真的不错
Come here, you gotta sit down.
过来 兄弟快坐下
Come here, come on.
快过来这里
Easy, easy.
慢慢地
There you go, there you go.
这就对了
Ah, Jesus.
我的天啊
You hang in there, buddy.
撑下去 兄弟
Okay, we're gonna get you fixed up.
我们会找人来治你的
All right? Okay.
好吗?
Guys, you wanna give me a hand here?
你们过来帮忙好吗?
Come on.
来吧
Take the left flank!
从左侧走!
从左侧走
"In the name of the Father and..."
奉圣父、圣子、圣灵之名赐福于你
Hey, Malark.
嘿 马拉其
You see what I'm seeing?
你也看到了吗?
"...is now, and ever shall be, world without end.
直到没有终点的世界
"Amen."
阿门
Crazy fools, the Irish.
疯狂的爱尔兰笨蛋
You should know.
你该知道的
Smokey, the window! Let's go!
史摩基 窗户 快点!
Morning, sir.
早上好 长官
What's your name, trooper?
你叫什么名字?
Sergeant Farmsworth from Able Company 501st.
501团Ａ连的法姆斯沃司中士
I'm supposed to tell you...
我要向你报告
...it's clear from here north...
我们已经清除从这里一直到北边的...
...of them Krauts, sir.
全部德军 长官
Well, tell your CO 506 arrived in force...
那去告诉你们的指挥官 506团已经抵达
...and secured all positions south of you.
并已巩固南边所有阵地
Yes, sir, I'll tell him.
是的 长官 我会告诉他
Come on, bad boy, let's go!
肥马 咱们走!
Lieutenant Winters.
温特斯中尉
Yes, sir?
什么事 长官?
Is it safe to cross now?
现在通过安全吗?
What's that, sir?
您说什么 长官?
Is it safe to cross?
现在通过安全吗?
We wanna move the wounded.
我们要搬运伤患
Yes, sir.
可以的 长官
Okay.
好的
Come on, let's get them out of here.
快把他们送走
There she is.
找到了
You're lucky it was a ricochet.
你真走运这只是颗跳弹
You just caught a piece of it.
你只是被碎片打到
Stupid.
真是愚蠢
What?
什么?
Nothing.
没什么
Walking wounded to the rear.
能走的伤员到后面去
Now, you gonna be able to stay off it?
你现在不用上前线了?
Doesn't look that way.
我可不这么想
Well, you gotta try, huh?
你得试试看的
What have we got planned, chief?
有什么计划 老大?
Well, we expect a counterattack.
我们得准备防范敌人的反扑
Carentan's as important to them as it is to us.
卡灵顿对他们和我们一样重要
Any idea when?
什么时候行动?
We're not waiting around to find out.
我们没时间坐在这里等了
Battalion wants us to head east to high ground...
营部要我们向东朝高地走
...set up a defensive position.
建立防御阵地
With the flooded fields...
这里到处都是沼泽
...it's the only direction they'd come from.
那是德军唯一进攻路线
Yeah.
对
You gonna be all right?
你没问题吧?
Yeah.
没问题
Good.
好极了
What's wrong with Blithe?
布洛依怎么了?
Well, nothing, except he can't see.
没事 只是看不见东西了
He can't see?
他看不见东西?
So he says.
他是这么说的
Blithe?
布洛依?
It's Lieutenant Winters.
我是温特斯中尉
What happened?
你怎么了?
I don't know, sir.
我不知道 长官
Things they just kind of went black on me.
只是眼前突然就变黑了
You can't see?
你看不见吗?
Not a thing, sir.
长官 我什么都看不见
I can't see a thing.
什么都看不见
Well, you just take it easy, Blithe.
放轻松点 布洛依
We're gonna get you out of here.
我们会带你离开这里
Get you back to England.
让你回到英国
It's gonna be okay.
不会有事的
Sir...
长官
...I didn't wanna let anyone down.
我不想让任何人失望
Just take it easy.
你放轻松就对了
It's okay, son.
没关系的孩子
Sir.
长官
Yeah, what is it?
什么事?
Thank you, sir.
谢谢你 长官
I'm okay.
我没事了
Yeah, I'm okay.
是的 没事了
I'm okay.
没事了
I think I'm okay.
我想我没问题了
You can see?
你看得见了?
God, I don't know what happened.
老天 我不知道发生什么事
I think, I think I'm okay.
我想我没事了
All right.
好吧
Well, stay here a little while longer...
你在这再待一会儿
...and make sure.
确定没事后
And, then you can report back to your platoon.
再向你排里报到
Yes, sir.
是 长官
Now, can we get that bandage on?
现在可以给你上绷带了吗?
Yeah.
好的
Berlin by Christmas.
我认为我们可以在圣诞节前攻下柏林
That's how I see it.
我也这么看
Yeah, you're full of it.
是啊 你在胡说八道
Oh, God.
天啊
This Kraut cheese tastes like...
这德国老的乳酪吃起来象...
It stinks.
臭死了
Bread's stale, too.
面包也坏了
Give me that.
给我
Yes, sir, the way we came in town today and took over...
长官 照我们今天攻下这个小镇的情况来看
...it don't seem Jerry's got much fight left.
德军的气数已尽
More, don't get hit in the face...
摩尔! 德军丢海绵时
...when Jerry throws in the sponge.
小心别被砸到脸 好吗?
You mark my words, Mal, Berlin by Christmas.
记住我的话 摩尔 圣诞节前攻下柏林
Enjoy it while it lasts.
趁现在享受一下
We'll be moving out, soon.
我们很快就要出发了
Out of town, Lieutenant? Already?
这么快就要离开了 中尉?
That's right.
没错
Don't they know we're just getting settled here?
难道他们不知道我们才刚进驻而已?
Nice, Groucho.
说得好 抱怨鬼
What?
什么?
Real smart.
自作聪明
You know, you're taking your life in your own hands.
你这是在自寻死路
Ain't that right?
对吧?
I told you, I didn't actually see it.
我说过...我没有亲眼看到
What, his shooting the prisoners...
史毕尔是射杀战俘
...or the sergeant in his platoon?
还是他自己排上的士官?
- Sergeant? - I didn't hear that one.
- 士官? - 这我可没听说
He shot one of his own guys?
等等 他杀了个自己人?
Well, supposedly the guy was drunk...
好象是这家伙喝醉了
...and refused to go on a patrol.
然后拒绝执行巡逻任务
Who knows if it's true.
谁知道是不是真的?
Well, I know a guy who said an eyewitness...
我认识一个人说有目击者说...
...told him that Speirs hosed those prisoners.
看到史毕尔屠杀了一群战俘
Why?
为什么?
What for?
为了什么?
On D-day.
在D日那天
Speirs comes across this group of Kraut prisoners...
史毕尔遇到一群受到严密看护
...digging a hole or some such under guard and all.
正在挖洞的德国战俘
He breaks out a pack of smokes...
他突然拆开一包烟
...passes them out.
然后一一发下去
He even gives them a light.
他甚至还帮他们点火
Then, all of a sudden...
然后 突然间
...he swings up his Thompson...
他亮出冲锋枪
...and he hoses them.
把他们全都毙了
I mean, goddamn, gives them smokes first?
我是说 天啊! 还先给他们烟抽?
You see, that's why I don't believe he really did it.
这就是为什么我不相信真的是他下的手
You don't believe it?
你不相信?
I heard he didn't do it.
我听说他没这么做
Oh, no, no, it was him all right.
不 就是他干的 没错
But it was more than eight guys.
但不止八个人
It was more like 20.
大约是二十个人
Hell of a shot.
杀的还真多
All except one guy...
他把他们全杀了
...who he left alone.
只留下一个人
Well, all I know, from what I heard...
就我所知 在D日
...he took that last 105 on D-day practically by himself.
他独自摧毁了最后一门105炮
Running through MG fire like a maniac.
象疯子一样穿越德军的机枪炮火
Yeah, that I did see.
这我有亲眼看到
- On his own? - Yeah
- 他一个人? - 没错!
I don't care if any of the other stuff's true.
我可不管其他的传言是真是假
Hey, Albert.
嘿 亚伯特
What do you think?
你怎么看?
I don't know.
我不知道
I'm gonna have to take everybody's word for it.
人家怎么说 我就怎么信
I didn't see any of it.
我什么都没有看见
Let's go, 1st Platoon, weapons on me.
第一排 咱们走带上武器
We're moving out.
我们出发了
Hey, take all your smokes.
别再抽烟了
On your feet, tactical column.
起立 成战术纵队
Flankers, up.
侧翼起立 出发了
That means you, Private Blithe.
我是在说你 布洛依
Come on, Blithe, get up.
布洛依 快起来
Hey, Luz? What?
鲁兹! 什么事?
How far we going?
我们要走多远?
Oh, Jesus Christ, Frank, I don't know.
法兰克 我也不知道
Until they tell us to stop.
直到他们叫我们停下来吧
High ground.
到高地
There's high ground up ahead.
就在前面的高地
Okay, genius, answer me this then:
好吧 天才! 那你告诉我
Why is Easy Company the only company who's either...
为什么Ｅ连是唯一的一个连
...at the front of an advance or, like now...
不是打前锋 就是象现在
...exposed at the far edge of the line?
暴露在战地最前线?
To keep you on your toes.
要你随时提高警觉
No, that's not what I'm saying.
这不是我的意思
I'm saying that we're never in the middle.
我是说我们从来没走在中间过
And we're the fifth of nine companies of this regiment.
我们是团里九个连的第五连
Able through Item.
从Ａ连到Ｉ连
Think of it.
你想想看
See there, you see that?
看到那里吗? 看到没有?
Incoming!
敌火射击!
Contact right!
右边遭遇敌火!
Get in the hedgerow!
躲进树丛里!
See what I mean?
明白我的意思了吧?
Left, bring it around!
往左侧!大家散开!
Stay low!
蹲下!
Luz, get down here with the radio now!
鲁兹 快把无线电拿来!
What have they got to sing about?
他们有什么好唱的?
Flash!
电闪!
Thunder.
雷鸣!
Catchy tune...
真是悦耳的歌声
...ain't it?
是吧?
Hey, Lieutenant, what's the news?
有什么消息吗?
Oh, same as it was this afternoon.
还是跟下午一样
They're in their hedgerow, we're in ours.
德军跟我们都撤回各自的树林
Spell me a minute, sir?
我可以休息一下吗?
Are you gonna let Blithe get some sack time?
你能让布洛依睡一下吗?
My back teeth are floating.
我后面的牙齿快掉了
Get back here ASAP, Martin.
快去快回 马丁
Count on me, sir.
你放心 长官
How you doing, Blithe?
你还好吗 布洛依?
I'm okay, sir.
我没事 长官
What happened at the aid station today?
今天在救护站是怎么回事?
Doc Roe...
罗医生
...called it hysterical blindness.
他说这叫歇斯底里性失明
No, thank you, sir.
不了 谢谢 长官
You know what they said on basic:
在入伍受训时 他们说
"Dehydration's a soldier's worst enemy."
脱水是军人最大的敌人
Yeah.
对了
It's a game, Blithe.
这只是一场球赛而已 布洛依
That's all.
就这么简单
Hell, we're just moving the ball forward...
我们只是将球一码一码
...one yard at a time.
向前推进
Nothing but a game.
只是一场球赛罢了
What is, sir?
什么象球赛 长官?
This. The whole thing.
这整个战争
No.
不了
Thank you, sir.
谢谢 长官
Just a game.
只是场球赛
Harry?
哈利
S-2 said the Germans only left a company to defend Carentan.
情报部门说德军只留下一个连防守卡灵顿
Yeah. The rest pulled out sometime last night.
其他人在昨晚撤走了
I knew that town was too easy.
我就知道那小镇太容易拿下了
Yeah.
没错
They regrouped south of town.
他们在小镇南方重新集结
May have been on their way to a counterattack...
我们可能会在此
...when we ran into them here.
遭到他们的反击
Strength unknown.
敌方兵力不详
They want the town back.
他们要夺回小镇
And we're in their way.
而我们阻止了他们
If they don't come first...
如果他们不先发动攻击
...we're attacking at first light, 0530.
我们就在5点30分发动拂晓攻击
I'll tell the men to fix bayonets.
我会叫弟兄们装上刺刀
Not much of a limp.
没有跛得很严重嘛
I'll survive.
我撑得下去
How is it?
感觉如何?
Hurts.
很痛
War is hell.
战争就象炼狱
Smith, wake up.
史密斯 醒醒
Come on, Smith.
起来 史密斯
Get up, it's your watch.
该你放哨了
Smith.
史密斯
It's your watch.
该你放哨了
Easy, Smith, it's me, Talbert.
别紧张 史密斯 是我 泰柏特
Smith, what the hell are you doing?
史密斯 你在千什么?
That's Talbert.
他是泰柏特
Goddamn.
可恶
Oh, gosh.
哦 天啊
Medic!
医务兵!
I'm sorry, I didn't mean to.
很抱歉 我不是故意的
He looked like a Kraut.
他看来象是德国人
I didn't know it was him.
我不知道是他
You gotta breathe.
你能呼吸吗?
Look at me, look at me.
看着我
Yeah, I can breathe!
我可以呼吸!
I'll put sulfur on the wound.
我要在伤口上撒些硫磺粉
You're gonna be fine.
佛洛依德 你会没事的
What the hell is that?
那是什么声音?
Sounds like it's coming from 3rd Platoon.
象是从第三排传来的
You wanna get some sleep?
你要不要睡一下?
I don't think, I don't think I can.
我不认为我睡的着
Then go take a look.
那就去瞧个究竟
Sarge.
中士
Flash.
电闪!
Thunder, thunder!
雷鸣!
Lieutenant Speirs, sir.
是史毕尔中尉吗?
Where are you going, Private?
你要去哪里?
Check out the noise, sir.
去查看那个叫声 长官
I just came from there.
我才从那儿过来
Everything's under control.
一切都在掌控之中
Yes, sir.
是 长官
Got some nervous privates in your company.
你连上的弟兄紧张了?
We do, sir.
是的 长官
Yeah, we do, I can vouch for that.
的确是 我可以向你保证
They just don't see how simple it is.
他们就是看不出来这是件多单纯的事
How simple what is, sir?
有多简单呢 长官?
Just do what you have to do.
只要做好你该做的事
Like you did on D-day, sir?
就象是你在D日做的吗?
Lieutenant.
中尉
Sir, when I landed on D-day...
D日当天我着陆以后
...I found myself in a ditch all by myself.
发现壕沟里只有我一个人
I fell asleep.
我睡着了
I think it was those air-sickness pills they gave us.
我想是因为那些 他们给的晕机药的关系
When I woke up, I didn't really try to find my unit...
当我醒来后 我并没有立刻去找我的部队
...to fight.
加入战斗
I just...
我只是...
I just kind of stayed put.
我只是待在原地不动
What's your name, trooper?
你叫什么名字 伞兵?
Blithe, sir.
布洛依 长官
Albert Blithe.
亚伯特・布洛依
You know why you hid in that ditch, Blithe?
你知道你为何躲在那个壕沟里吗 布洛依?
I was scared.
因为我害怕
We're all scared.
我们都很害怕
You hid in that ditch because you think there's still hope.
你躲在那个壕沟里 是因为你觉得还有希望
But, Blithe, the only hope you have is to accept the fact...
可是你唯一的希望就是...
...that you're already dead.
把自己当成已死的人
And the sooner you accept that...
你越早接受这一点
...the sooner you'll function...
就能越早发挥...
...as a soldier's supposed to function.
一个士兵应有的功能
Without mercy, without compassion...
不带怜悯 不带同情
...without remorse.
不带悔恨
All war depends upon it.
所有的战争都靠它
( D日后第7天 )
( 卡灵顿外围地带 )
Got any smokes?
有烟吗?
Want this candy shit?
你要来点这种烂烟吗?
No, I'm all right.
不要
The outpost got ammo.
外围哨所里有弹药
Here you go, guys.
拿去吧
No, we don't know what they've got.
不 我们不知道他们有多少人
We may be attacking a weaker force...
我们可能在攻击一个小部队
...possibly more paratroopers.
可能大部分是伞兵
And you know how they can be.
而且你知道他们的战法
Fire and maneuver.
"打带跑"
That's the name of the game, fire and maneuver.
就是这场游戏的名字
Dog and Fox Companies will be on our left flank, moving with us.
Ｄ连和Ｆ连会在左翼和我们一起前进
Any questions?
有疑问吗?
Let's make them holler.
去打得他们哭爹喊娘吧
It's 9:30 in the evening back home.
现在在家乡是晚上9点30分
Must be.
一定是
Mortar!
迫击炮!
Incoming!
敌火攻击!
Down, down, down, down!
趴下!
Get that OP in!
去叫通信兵过来!
Tell them to hold, I'm checking the lines.
叫他们等一下 我正在检查防线
All Easy stations, Easy Six.
Ｅ连注意 这是E6号呼叫
Hold in position, over.
所有人留在原地 完毕
Go, lock and load!
快 上膛开保险!
Easy Six, Easy Red Six.
呼叫E6 这里是E红6号
I've got mortars all across my line.
迫击炮落在我的防线上
No sign of infantry yet.
没有看到敌人步兵的踪迹
I'm pulling the OP in, over.
通话结束 完毕
Right plus 15, charge three.
向右 向上15度! 3号装弹药!
Range, 600.
距离600公尺
Come on, move it, move it, hurry!
走吧 快点!
Watch for silhouettes on the horizon!
注意地平线上的黑影!
Keep low, go, go, go!
蹲下点!快走!
Perconte!
派康提!
Get your men in order!
叫你的弟兄不要慌张!
Stay low!
蹲下!
Pour it at them, Perconte.
集中火力射击
To your left.
攻击你的左边
Keep going, keep going.
继续走
Keep it up!
别停!
I want fire superiority!
我要优势火力!
Guarnere, keep them pinned down.
叫你的人蹲下
Keep firing!
继续射击!
Sir, just reverse!
长官 反方向!
Cover the crest of that hill!
射击那座山顶!
Where in the hell did they come from?
敌人是从哪儿冒出来的?
Holy shit, there goes our left flank!
可恶 左翼完蛋了
Sir, Dog and Fox are pulling back.
长官! Ｄ连和Ｆ连撤退了
What?
什么?
Who gave that order, God damn it?
是谁下的命令?可恶
Keep firing, stay low!
继续射击 蹲下点!
Stay low, keep firing, Perconte.
蹲下 继续射击 派康提
Come on, Blithe!
来吧 布洛依!
Stand up!
站起来!
Get up on your feet, soldier.
给我站起来 士兵
Get up, Blithe.
站起来 布洛依
That's right, Blithe.
就是这样 布洛依
You can do it!
你办的到的!
Fire your weapon, Blithe.
开火 布洛依
Hit those goddamn Germans, Blithe!
打那些可恶的德国人 布洛依!
Keep firing!
继续射击!
Let them have it.
给他们好看
Keep firing!
继续射击!
Don't slack it off.
不要松懈
Let them have it, Blithe!
给他们好看 布洛依!
Pour it on them, Blithe!
向他们开枪 布洛依!
Get some men up there!
派些人到上面去!
Move it!
快去!
Let's go, McGrath, on me.
来 麦格加斯 听我口令
Shift your fire right.
移到右侧射击
Down, down!
卧倒!
Come on!
快点!
You're gonna get me killed, Lieutenant.
你会害死我的 中尉
I knew you'd get me killed.
我就知道你会害死我
Don't fire till I tell you, McGrath.
听我命令开火 麦格加斯
I knew you were gonna get me killed.
我就知道你会把我害死
Hold your fire!
还不可以射击!
No, that's too close!
不行 这样太近了!
Bitch, son of a bitch!
- 该死的王八蛋! - 太近了!
Medic!
医护兵!
Go now.
快点!
Now, fire, McGrath!
开始射击!
Fire!
射击!
Covering fire!
掩护射击!
Keep firing south.
掩护射击
You hit a home run, huh?
你打了个全垒打
Smith, I've been hit.
史密斯 我中弹了
Just get me out of here!
带我离开这里
Medic!
医护兵!
You okay?
- 你没事吧? - 没事!
Move it, move it!
快走!
Rounds complete!
弹药用完了!
Skip, more ammo!
史基普 再拿弹药来!
Go, go!
快点!
On my way.
马上去!
Medic!
医护兵!
Jesus, what was that?
老天 那是什么?
Shermans.
谢尔曼坦克
Well, hello, 2nd Armored.
第二装甲师 你好啊
That's right, you sorry asses.
没错 你们这些可怜虫
Run!
快逃吧!
Oh, you beautiful babies, you!
你们真是漂亮的宝贝!
Let's go!
我们上!
Pour it on them!
狠狠地打!
Let them have it, come on!
让他们尝尝厉害!
Check it out, Shermans.
你看 是谢尔曼坦克
About damn time.
也该是时候了
Come on!
杀啊!
Come on.
来吧
Go to Lt. Kick their ass. Don't let them rest.
踢他们的屁股 别让他们歇着
Hey, buddy?
嘿 兄弟
Hey, buddy, you okay?
你还好吗?
Looks like you fellows had a heck of a fight.
你们看来好象打了一场硬战
Move forward on the right flank.
向前移动到右翼
( D日后第25天 )
We need to know what's in there.
我们得知道那里的情况
I don't know who the hell to send.
我根本不知道该叫谁去
Ask for volunteers.
找自愿者
I hate asking for volunteers.
我最讨厌找自愿者
Then pick them.
那就选一个
Need to take a look at that farmhouse.
我需要有人去查看那个农舍
Who wants to go?
有谁愿意去吗?
I'll go.
我愿意去
Anybody else?
还有谁?
Martin, Dukeman, you just volunteered.
马丁! 杜克曼 你们也自愿去
Hubba-hubba.
真棒
I'll be lead.
我带队
Blithe's lead scout, move out.
布洛依带领搜索组 出发!
Harry...
哈利
...what exactly are you doing with your reserve chute?
你的副伞是怎么回事?
You been hauling that thing around ever since we jumped?
你从跳完伞后 就一直拖着那玩意?
Gonna send it to Kitty when we get back to England.
我要在回英国后送给琪蒂
Silk.
丝质的
Figure it'll make a good wedding dress, you know?
我想把它当作婚纱的料子应该不错
What with rationing and all.
再配上些缀饰
Jeez, Harry, I never would have guessed.
哈利 我没料到你会这样
What?
怎样?
That I'm so sentimental?
没想到我这么多愁善感?
No, that you think we're gonna make it back to England.
不是 你还真以为我们能够活着回英国
Okay.
好的
Here we go again.
又来了
Covering fire, covering fire!
掩护射击!
Go, go!
快走!
Hang in there, Blithe.
撑着点 布洛依
Come on.
来吧
Keep moving down!
保持低姿势!
Medic here!
医护兵!
Top window right!
右边最上面的窗户!
Hang in there.
撑着点
Medic!
医护兵!
We need a medic down here!
我们这里需要医护兵!
Cease fire, cease fire!
停止射击!
Take it easy, Blithe.
放轻松点 布洛依
Take it easy.
放轻松
Come on, Duke, come on.
坚持 杜克 坚持
Move, move.
闪开
Coming through, give me room.
借过
Out of my way.
让开点
I got it.
我来处理
What happened?
怎么回事?
Sniper.
狙击手
All right, Blithe, I got you.
好了 布洛依 我来了
Nice and easy, nice and easy.
慢慢的
They're pulling us off the front line.
他们要我们撤离前线
Now?
现在?
To a field camp north of Utah Beach.
到犹他海滩北边的一个野战营区
Hot food.
有热食
And showers.
还能洗澡
Then back to England.
然后回去英国
Harry.
哈利
How's the leg?
你的腿怎么样?
Stiff. Sore.
又僵硬 又酸!
They want me to take it easy for a few days.
他们要我休息几天
Yeah, you should.
你是该休息了
Talked to Colonel Sink.
刚跟辛克上校谈过话
Said he appreciated Easy holding the line.
他说很感激Ｅ连...守住了防线
Said General Taylor was pleased.
还说 泰勒将军很高兴
That's why I came to France.
那就是我来法国的原因
To please General Taylor.
为了让泰勒将军高兴
Yeah.
是啊
In grateful acknowledgement...
为了表达对你们...
...of the bloodshed in service of your country...
效忠国家浴血奋战的肯定
...it is my honor to present you...
我十分荣幸为你们颁发...
...with the order of the Purple Heart.
紫心勋章
Thank you, sir.
谢谢你 长官
How many's that make?
你拿了几枚了?
Two?
两枚?
Three?
三枚?
You have no shame.
你真是不知羞耻
Hey, I got one hole in my shoulder...
我肩膀有穿了个洞
...a second in my calf...
膝盖上又有一个洞
...and a boil on my shin that had to be lanced.
小腿上的脓疮还得用刀挖掉
And he only gets one.
而他却只拿了一枚
This is great.
真棒
She fancied me, Alton.
她喜欢我 艾尔顿
Jesus Christ!
老天!
It's good to be alive!
活着的感觉真好!
Jesus Christ, that sure was close.
我的天啊 刚刚真险
Nah, missed him by a mile.
还差一里远呢
Hey, Hoobler.
嘿 胡伯勒
Be quiet for the man.
安静一下
What?
什么事?
The Night of the Bayonet.
"刺刀之夜"
"The night was filled with dark and cold
那晚又冷又黑
"When Sergeant Talbert
当泰柏特中士...
"The story's told, pulled on his poncho
故事是这样说的 他披着雨衣
"And headed out
要外出检查防线
"To check the lines dressed like a Kraut"
却穿的象个德国佬
Why is everyone in such a hurry to get back?
为何大家都急着回去?
Hospital food don't suit you?
吃不惯医院里的伙食吗?
We don't need you anymore.
我们不需要你了
"Upon a trooper our hero came
英雄来到某人床前
"Fast asleep, he called his name
那人睡得烂熟 他叫着那人的名字
"Oh, Smith
史密斯!
"Get up, it's time
起床了
To take your turn out on the line"
该你出去警戒了
Do you guys have any idea what he's talking about?
你们谁知道他在说什么?
The Night of the Bayonet.
"刺刀之夜"
Whatever that is.
不管那是什么
"So very weary
史密斯好疲倦
"Cracked an eye, all red and bleary
睡眼朦胧 撑开红红的眼睛
"Grabbed his rifle, he did not tarry
抓着他的来复枪 一点也没耽搁
"Hearing Floyd but seeing Jerry"
耳里听到是佛洛依德 却眼花看成是德国佬
Way to go, Smithy.
干得好 史密斯
"'It's me,' cried Tab
"是我!"泰柏特大叫
"'Don't do it,' and yet Smith charged
"别动手!"可是史密斯冲上前
"Tout de suite, with bayonet
挥舞刺刀杀红了眼
"He lunged, he thrust, both high and low
他上戳下刺 左剁右砍
"And skewered the boy from Kokomo"
把这科可摩来的小子当成肉串
I'm heading back to barracks.
我要回兵营了
You Heffron?
你是赫夫朗吗?
Yeah.
是啊
Where you from?
你从哪里来?
Who's asking?
你是哪位?
You from Philadelphia?
你是从费城来的吗?
South Philly, yeah.
是啊 费城南区
I could tell.
我看得出来
17th Street.
我在第17街
Front Street.
是吗?我住你前面一条街
Hey.
嘿
Come here, sit down.
过来坐吧
Hey, you know a guy named Johnny Waylon?
你知不知道有个叫强尼威龙的人?
Yeah, I know Johnny.
我认识强尼
Yeah, tar-head, yeah.
我们以前都管他叫柏油头
As you weren't wounded by the enemy...
因为你不是被敌人所伤
...and thus didn't qualify for a Purple Heart...
所以不能被颁受紫心勋章
...we've taken matters into our own hands.
我们就自己来表扬这件事
Tab, this is for you.
泰仔 这是给你的
That's right.
没错
I could have shot the kid a dozen times.
我当时可朝这小子开了好几枪
Yeah, right.
没错
I just didn't think we could spare a man.
我以为我们人手不够
Couple of announcements, men.
各位 我有一些事要宣布
First, listen up.
首先! 注意听好了
First, the training exercise scheduled for 2200 has been cancelled.
原订在晚上十点的训练取消了
Oh, yeah.
太好了
Secondly...
再者
...all passes are hereby revoked.
所有休假都取消了
We're heading back to France.
我们要回法国去
So, pack up all your gear.
所以把你们的装备都准备好
We will not be returning to England, boys.
我们不再呆在英国了
Anyone who has not made out a will...
还没立下遗嘱的
...go to the supply office.
到补给室办理
The trucks depart for Membury at 0700.
前往孟伯瑞的卡车...早上七点出发
As you were.
你们继续吧
Hello?
有人吗?
有人在吗?
Good morning, Miss Lamb.
早安 蓝太太
Sorry to bother you so early.
很抱歉一大早吵醒你
That's all right.
没关系
Private...
你是二等兵
Malarkey.
马拉其
Come in.
请进
Actually, it's Sergeant Malarkey now, ma'am. I just got promoted.
事实上! 我刚被晋升为中士
Oh, lovely.
真好
I expect you want your laundry.
我猜你们会来拿衣服
I heard the trucks rumbling by all night.
整晚都听到卡车的隆隆声
I guess the Yanks must be on their way off again.
我就猜美国佬又要上路了
Yes, ma'am.
是的
Looks like for good this time.
看来是不会回来了
I'm sorry to hear that.
很遗憾听到这消息
Two shirts, two pairs of trousers...
两件衬衫 两条长裤
...light starch.
稍微烫一下
Two bob and tuppence, please.
一共是两先令两便士
Thank you.
谢谢你
谢谢
Would you like a cup of tea?
你想要来杯茶吗?
I've got the water boiling.
我烧了开水
No, no, thank you.
不用了 谢谢你
I'm in a hell of a...
我有点赶时间
...bit of a hurry but thank you anyway.
不过还是谢谢你
Oh, Private?
士兵?
Yes, ma'am.
什么事?
Lieutenant Meehan's one of yours, isn't he?
米汉中尉是你们队上的吧?
I hope he hasn't forgotten his laundry.
希望他没忘了来拿衣服
I'll take it.
我帮他拿去
Thank you.
谢谢你
You, you couldn't be a dear...
你可不可以帮个忙
...and help me with a few others, could you?
也帮其他人拿?
Let's see.
我看看
Sergeant Evans.
依凡斯中士
Private Moya.
二等兵摩亚
Blowzer.
布劳泽
Gray.
葛瑞
Miller.
米勒
Owen.
欧文
Collins.
柯林斯
Elliot.
艾略特
Blithe.
布洛依
Ｅ连6月29日撤离前线之前 已失去65名弟兄
亚伯特・布洛依在诺曼底受的伤始终没有痊愈 于1948年去世